Okay, welcome to session three.
好的，欢迎来到第三节课。
We're going to cover two more musical concepts, ties and dots,
我们将讨论另外两个音乐概念，延音线和附点，
before we're ready to move on to the next section.
在我们准备好进入下一节之前。
Let's talk about ties first,
让我们先来谈谈延音线，
the problem we have is,
我们的问题是，
we need to have long notes in music,
我们需要在音乐中有长的音符，
now whole note will hold for four beats we learned about that,
全音符可以保持四个节拍，我们已经学过了，
but what if I want to hold for six beats
但是如果我想保持六个节拍，
or eight or something beyond a bar line,
或者八个节拍，或者其他节拍超过小节线，
how do we do that,
我们怎么才能做到，
well, we cover that problem with a thing called a tie,
我们用一种叫做延音线的东西来解决这个问题，
that arc line that you see,
你看到的那条弧形线，
over those two notes,
在这两个音符上，
that is what's called tie
这就是所谓的延音线，
and it is linking those two notes together,
它将这两个音符连接在一起，
so as you're seeing in that first example,
就像你在第一个例子中看到的，
the whole note is tied over the bar line to the half note,
全音符通过小节线连接到二分音符，
how this is played,
这是怎么弹的，
the half note gets two beats, the whole note gets four beats,
二分音符是两拍，全音符是四拍，
so I add all those together,
所以我把这些加在一起，
I don't replay that half note,
我没有重弹二分音符，
when I get to it,
当我到达它的时候，
I just give its two beats to the whole note
我只是把它的两个节拍加到全音符上，
to make a total of six beats,
总共是六个节拍，
see how that works,
看到它是如何工作的吗，
I'm just tying those two notes together,
我只是把这两个音符连接在一起，
I don't replay that second note,
我不重弹第二个音符，
I just add them both together.
我只是把它们加在一起。
In example two, you'll see a quarter note, half note
在例子二中，你会看到一个四分音符，二分音符，
and then a quarter note that's tied over the bar line to a note of the same pitch,
然后一个四分音符通过小节线连接到一个相同音高的音符，
ties are always to the note of the same pitch,
延音线总是在相同音高的音符，
you're never going to see it going between different pitches,
你永远不会看到它在不同的音调之间，
they're going between different pitches, that's what's called a slur
它们在不同的音调之间，这就是所谓的圆滑线，
and we don't really see those too much in guitar music.
我们在吉他音乐中不太能看到这种情况。
So, the tie goes over the bar line
所以，延音线通过小节线，
with those quarter notes, then another quarter note
一个四分音符，然后另一个四分音符，
and then a half note tied over to a whole note.
然后一个二分音符连接到一个全音符。
So if I was to play this,
所以如果我要演奏这个，
I'm just going to do on a first string E,
我要演奏第一个弦 E ，
and I'll play that example 2,
我会演奏示例 2 ，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
one, one two,
1 ，1 2 ，
tied over the bar line here,
延音线通过小节线，
one two, one two three four,
1 2 ， 1 2 3 4 ，
see how that works.
看这是怎么工作的。
The next concept, we need to talk about is dots,
下一个概念，我们需要讨论的是附点，
now dots add something to the note,
附点在音符上添加一些东西，
dots add, here's the rule,
附点添加，这是规则，
dots add one half of whatever they're attached to,
附点添加它们所连接的音符的一半，
what do I mean by that,
我这么说是什么意思，
well let's look at our example,
让我们看看我们的例子，
in our half note example,
在我们的二分音符的例子中，
I have a half note with a dot on it,
我有一个二分音符，上面有一个圆点，
a half note gets two beats,
二分音符有两个节拍，
the dot, what is the dot get,
附点带来什么，
the dot gets half of whatever it's attached to,
附点得到它所连接的任何音符的一半，
so half note gets two, the dot would then get one,
所以二分音符得到 2 ，附点得到 1 ，
so you add them all up together and that gets three.
所以你把它们加在一起，得到 3 。
Our next example is a whole note,
我们的下一个例子是一个全音符，
what if I put a dot on a whole note,
如果我在全音符上加一个附点，
usually about this stage,
通常在这种情况，
everybody gets it,
每个人都明白，
I get it, a dot adds one,
我知道一个点加一，
well, it's a little more to it than that,
好的，应该比它多一点，
if it's attached to a half note, it adds one,
如果它附加到一个二分音符上，它加一，
if it's attached to a whole note, it adds more than that,
如果它附加到一个全音符上，它加更多，
let's figure it out, a dotted whole note,
让我们算一下，一个加附点的全音符，
the whole note gets four,
全音符是 4 ，
the dot, what is the dot get,
附点能得到什么，
half of whatever it's attached to,
它附加的音符的一半，
half of four is two,
4 的一半是 2 ，
four plus two is six,
4 加 2 等于 6 ，
so a dotted whole note is going to be six,
所以一个加附点的全音符将是 6 ，
you're going to see that very much,
你们会经常看到，
but I wanted you to see the difference between the other one,
但我想让你们看到另一个之间的区别，
here's what you're going to see a little bit more.
这是你们将会看到的。
A dotted quarter note,
带附点的四分音符，
now think about what would this be,
现在想一下，这是什么，
the quarter note gets one
四分音符得到一，
and the dot what would the dot get,
附点得到什么，
the dot would just get a half,
附点会得到一半，
because it's half of whatever it's attached to
因为它是它所依附的一半，
and it's attached to just one,
它依附于一，
so one plus a half be one and a half,
所以 1 加上 1/2 是 1 又 1/2 ，
and that would make up a complete beat,
这将构成一个完整的节拍，
but usually you'd see it followed by another eighth note
但通常你会看到它后面跟着另一个八分音符，
and that's how they make those rhythms work.
这就是他们如何使这些节奏发挥作用的。
And that's ties and dots.
这就是延音线和附点。
Okay, let's talk about eighth notes,
好的，现在我们来谈谈八音符，
now eighth notes are part of that group of rhythms that we talked about at the very beginning,
八分音符是我们在一开始谈到的那组节奏的一部分，
whole notes get four beats,
全音符是四拍，
half notes get two beats,
二分音符是两拍，
quarter notes get one beat
四分音符是一拍，
and now we're going to subdivide that one beat,
现在我们要拆分一个节拍，
we're gonna split the one beat,
我们将拆分一个节拍，
and we're going to go to eighth notes,
我们要讲到八分音符，
which will each get a half a beat,
每个音符有半拍，
now as it's played on the guitar,
因为它是在吉他上演奏的，
when you have several of the same note on the same string,
当你在同一根弦上有几个相同的音符时，
you would alternate your picking,
你会调整拨片，
remember what we did in that first session,
记得我们在第一节课上做的，
we did a finger pattern of down up down up,
我们做了一个手指模式，下上，下上，
that we're going to apply that now and we're working with eighth notes,
我们现在要用第八个音符，
if the notes are the same pitch,
如果音符是相同的音高，
let's say you had a bunch of Es in a row,
假设你有一排 E ，
then instead of just going down down down down down down down,
那么不只是下 下 下 下 下 下 下，
you just go down up down up,
你使用下上下上，
so I wouldn't go down down down down,
所以我不会下 下 下 下，
I would go down up down up.
我会下上下上。
Now one more thing about eighth notes,
还有一件关于八分音符的事情，
when eighth notes are by themselves,
当八分音符是独立的，
they have a flag on the stem,
它们有一个符尾在符干上，
you have the note head, you have a stem, you have a little flag on it,
它上面有符头，符干，符尾，
when they're together, they're grouped,
当它们在一起的时候，它们被组合在一起，
when or when there's more than one,
当有超过一个时，
whether there's two a group of more,
不论是两个还是更多，
they're grouped together in twos usually
它们通常是两个被组合在一起，
and they use a beam across the top of them,
它们使用符杠在它们上面，
so that's what you'll see when that beam is,
所以这就是你会看到的符杠，
you may be confused about what that might be,
你可能会困惑那可能是什么，
those are just eighth notes tied together,
这些只是连接在一起的八分音符，
somebody figured out a hundred fifty years ago,
150 年前有人发现，
that when you have a bunch of eighth notes in a row,
当你有一串连续的八分音符时，
it's kind of difficult to read them,
阅读起来比较困难，
they have all those flags,
当它们有符尾时，
so they just beam them together,
所以用符杠把它们连接起来，
makes it a little bit easier to read.
让它更容易阅读。
So let's go through some of the eighth notes exercises in your book,
所以让我们来看看你书中的一些八分音符练习，
let's look at a eighth exercise number one,
让我们来看看八分音符练习一，
that's on your first, E string,
在你的第一弦， E 弦上，
we talked about down up down up,
我们讨论了下上下上，
when we get to the eighth notes,
当我们有八分音符时，
let's play,
我们开始，
down down, down up, down up,
下下，下上，下上，
now next note F,
现在下一个音符 F ，
down up, down, down,
下上，下，下，
back to E, down, down up, down, two.
回到 E ，下，下上，下， 2 。
Got it,
明白了吗，
see how those downs and ups work,
看看这些下和上是如何工作的，
now that really only applies when it's of the note of the same pitch,
只有相同音高的音符，这些才适用，
when you have a bunch of the same note in a row,
只有当你连续有一串相同的音符时，
now you'll find out really quickly as we go through these exercises,
你很快会发现，当你练习的时候，
as you're jumping strings and stuff,
当你跳过弦的时候，
you really can't hold true to that down and up alternating pattern all the time,
你不能一直保持这种上下交替的模式，
it just doesn't work out that way,
它不会以那种方式工作，
your brain will figure that out pretty quickly,
你的大脑会很快弄明白，
but only when you have notes of the same pitch on the same line,
但只有当你在同一行上有相同音调的音符时，
that you start doing alternating you'll be a little bit faster doing it that way.
你使用交替会更快一点。
Let's do a couple more, exercise number two.
让我们再做几个，第二个练习。
This one starts on second string, first finger, C,
这个从第二弦食指 C 开始，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
rest, now up to G,
休息，切换到 G ，
down these notes alternating your picking with each one and rest.
降低这些音符，使用拨片交替弹，然后休息。
Okay, we're going to do exercise four now,
好的，我们现在要做练习四了，
okay, I'm going to do a little bit faster,
好的，我要做得更快一点，
so you try and do the best you can.
所以你要试着尽你所能。
Ready go,
准备，开始，
two three four
2 3 4 ，
and that's how eighth notes work,
这就是八分音符的工作方式，
now let's learn a few more notes.
现在让我们再学习几个音符。
Okay, let's talk about the notes on the third string,
好的，让我们来讨论一下第三弦上的音符，
remember what the name of that third string is,
记住第三弦的名字是什么，
that's a G,
它是 G ，
okay, G is open, and that will be our first note,
G 是空弦的，这是我们的第一个音符，
the middle, excuse me, the second line on your music notation is A G,
中间的，抱歉，乐谱上的第二行是 G ，
that's this third string open,
这是空的第三弦，
the next note we have is
下一个音符是，
our second finger, our first second finger note we had is an A,
我们的第一个中指音符是 A ，
second space up,
第二个空格，
make sure you're fretting the note nice
确保你把音符按好，
and close to that fret not on the fret,
靠近品丝而不在品丝上面，
right back, so we have G
回来，所以我们有 G ，
and we have A,
我们有 A ，
play with me, G and now A.
和我一起弹， G 和 A 。
Very good, let's add those to our other notes,
非常好，我们把这些加到我们的其他音符上，
we've got G and A
我们有 G 和 A ，
and now let's do B C and D on the next string,
现在我们在下一个弦上弹 B C D ，
B C D,
B C D ，
on the next string, we've got E F and G,
在下一根弦上，我们有 E F G ，
E F and G,
E F G ，
can you go backwards,
你能倒退吗，
can you go backwards, the other way,
你能倒退吗，反过来，
G F E, D C B, A G.
G F E ， D C B ， A G 。
Very good, let's do one or two of these third string exercises,
非常好，让我们做一两个第三弦的练习，
let's do the first one,
我们来做第一个，
number one, you ready,
第一个，你准备好了吗，
starts on G, third string open,
从 G 开始，第三弦空弦，
ready play,
准备，开始，
G two, now A two,
G 2 ，现在 A 2 ，
then three Gs one two,
然后是三个 G ，
now A, make good contact with that A,
现在是 A ，很好地联系起来 A ，
back to G.
回到 G 。
Great, let's let's go to number two,
好的，让我们看第二个，
throw in some eighth notes on it,
在上面加一些八分音符，
ready, play,.
准备，开始，
Okay, let's talk about the notes on the fourth string,
好的，让我们来谈谈第四弦上的音符，
we're going to cover three more notes now in the fourth string,
我们会再讲第四弦上的三个音符，
the open string is it D,
空弦是 D ，
now look at the music notation,
现在来看一下乐谱，
it's going to be underneath the staff,
它将在五线谱下面，
this is our first one that's been out of our staff range,
这是我们第一个超出乐谱范围的音符，
the D is going to be below the staff
D 将在五线谱之下，
and that's fourth string open D,
这是第四弦空弦 D ，
the next note is with our second finger E
下一个音符是我们的中指 E ，
and the third note is with our third finger F.
第三个音符是我们的无名指 F ，
Let's do those again,
我们再来一次，
D E and F.
D E F 。
Let's try a couple of these fourth string exercises,
让我们尝试几个第四弦练习，
if you look at the first one,
如果你看第一个，
starts out with a D on a half note,
以二分音符的 D 开始，
let's play,
我们来弹奏，
ready go,
准备，开始，
then E,
然后 E ，
then F, two three four,
然后 F ， 2 3 4 ，
stays on that F, one two,
保持在那个 F 上， 1 2 。
very good.
非常好。
Let's check out number two,
我们来看看第二个，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
now, look at all these Fs, make sure alternate,
现在，看看所有这些 F ，确保交替，
down up, down up,
下上，下上，
there you go.
就是这样。
Just for fun,
只是为了好玩，
let's check out number four at the bottom of the page,
让我们来看看页面底部的第四个，
little, this would gets quite intense with all the notes in there,
有那么多音符，会变得相当紧张，
but I think you'll do it.
但我认为你会完成的。
Ready, play,
准备，弹奏，
quarter note here,
这里是四分音符，
then back down.
然后回来。
Okay, let's try that one one more time,
好的，让我们再试一次，
try, it's good, it's good exercise to try say the notes too,
试着说出音符是好的，
when you're playing them,
当你演奏它们的时候，
it helps your brain connect where they're at,
这有助于你的大脑连接，它们在哪里，
especially with these newer notes.
特别是在这些更新的音符上。
Ready go,
准备，开始，
A B C D E F G,
A B C D E F G ，
now we come back down,
现在我们回来，
G F E D C B A G F E D.
G F E D C B A G F E D 。
Now, at this stage,
现在，在这个阶段，
probably some of you're, you're going to start misfiring a little bit,
你可能会开始有一点失误，
you're going for the third string, you hit the fourth string,
你要弹第三弦，却碰到了第四弦，
you're going for the second string, you hit the third string,
你要去弹第二弦，却碰到了第三弦，
that is perfectly natural, right,
这是非常自然的，
right here in this stage of development,
在这个发展阶段，
just make sure you're bracing, you've got your bracing happening solid
只要确保你的支撑稳固，
and if you and that you go slow enough,
如果弹得足够慢，
some of these exercises, I may be going faster than you're at right now,
其中一些练习可能我会比你现在的速度快，
just just stop the tape, practice it a little bit on your own,
只要把录像停下来，自己练习一下，
and then you'll be ready to go, when it's time for us to play together.
然后到我们一起弹的时候，你就能跟上了。
Okay, welcome to the guitar tips, section of session three,
好的，欢迎来到第三节的吉他技巧部分，
we're going to talk about,
我们将谈论，
what I, what I think is one of the most practical things and helpful things
我认为最实用和最有帮助的事情之一，
you can do to improve yourself as a player
作为演奏者，你可以用来提高自己，
is working with a metronome,
就是使用节拍器，
metronome is a little thing like this,
节拍器是一个像这样的小东西，
they have also when that are the tick tock kind that go back and forth,
它们有滴答滴答的那种来回移动，
they both do the same thing,
它们都做同样的事情，
it just clicks off the tempo,
它只是在节奏上发出响声，
okay, and working with a metronome is although frustrating at first,
好的，使用节拍器工作虽然一开始很令人沮丧，
is very very good for helping you settle down your time,
对帮助你稳定时间很有帮助，
settle down your rhythm in these different exercises,
在这些不同的练习中稳定你的节奏，
so let me just show you how this works.
所以让我来向你展示一下它是如何工作的。
I'm going to turn it on,
我要把它打开，
and this is clicking off,
这是在点击，
let's see what does that say, 72 beats per minute,
让我们来看看这是什么意思，每分钟 72 次，
and so I was playing along with it,
所以我就顺着它演奏，
let's say, I'm playing a C chord, two three four,
比如，我演奏 C 和弦， 2 3 4 ，
I want to half notes,
我想要二分音符，
quarter notes.
四分音符。
Good, see how that works,
好的，看到它是如何工作的，
it really forces you to be honest,
它会迫使你诚实，
sometimes if you're sitting and practicing,
有时如果你坐着练习，
you know just sitting on the couch practicing,
坐在沙发上练习，
you'll kind of let yourself get sloppy
你会让自己变得有点邋遢，
and you won't to be real steady
你不会真正的稳定，
and you'll be doing a completely unsteady,
你会完全不稳定，
a metronome will let you do that,
节拍器会让你这么做，
it allow, it kind of forces you to be in tempo.
它会让你保持节奏。
And when it's time to speed up,
当你加速的时候，
I raise it up a little bit,
我把它调高了一点，
let's raise it up to let's say 92,
让我们把它提高到 92 ，
I'm going to do the same thing, C chord,
我会做同样的事情， C 和弦，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
one two three four,
1 2 3 4 ，
half notes,
二分音符，
quarter notes,
四分音符，
I can switch between chords,
我可以在和弦之间切换，
I can do single notes,
我可以做单音符，
working with a metronome,
使用节拍器，
probably one of the best things you can do.
可能是你能做的最好的事情之一。
Next thing I want to talk about in our guitar tips is
接下来我想在我们的吉他技巧中谈到的是，
holding your notes out,
拿起你的音符，
if you have a really really long note,
如果你有一个非常长的音符，
let's say a G here on the first string
假设第一弦上有一个很长的音符，
and I need to hold that out,
我需要坚持，
if I've got a tie, I'm holding into the next measure,
如果我有一个延音线，坚持到下一个小节，
I've got a really,
我有一个，
the guitar naturally decays,
吉他自然衰变，
it's one of the instruments,
它是一种乐器，
that doesn't really hold its, keep having to refresh the note,
不能保持、刷新它的音符，
so being that it has a very quick decay time,
所以它有非常快的衰减时间，
when you play that G,
当你弹奏 G 的时候，
you really gotta keep that finger on to get the most that you can out of that note,
你要把手指尽可能多地放在音符上面，
while it's playing,
当它演奏的时候，
you don't want to just play it,
你不想只演奏它，
if it's a whole note,
如果它是一个全音符，
just play it and then go on to the next note,
只演奏它，然后继续到下一个音符，
you got to hold these notes out,
你必须保持这些音符，
keep the pressure on through those long notes.
对那些长音符保持压力。
Also, now that we've introduced some new notes,
另外，现在我们引入了一些新的音符，
you'll notice that,
你们会注意到，
we've got two of different kinds of notes,
我们有两种不同的音符，
now we've got two Ds, we've got a low and a high,
现在我们有两个 D ，一个低的和一个高的，
we got two Es, a low and a high,
我们有两个 E ，一个低的和一个高的，
we've got two Fs,
我们有两个 F ，
and last we have two of Gs,
最后我们有两个 G ，
now, if you writing in notes
现在，如果你写下音符，
and I would encourage you to write notes, if you need to.
如果你需要的话，我鼓励你写下音符。
Sometimes we get into the habit
有时我们养成了习惯，
of just looking at the tops of the lines
就是只看着上面的线，
and looking at the notes we've written in
看着我们写的音符，
and will miss whether it's a low G or high G,
会错过它是低音 G 还是高音 G ，
how am I supposed to keep that straight,
我该如何保持直截了当，
you gotta look at the music,
你必须看乐谱，
if that note is in the staff second line,
如果那个音符在乐谱的第二线，
that's the lower G,
它是低音 G ，
if it's up on top of the staff,
如果它在乐谱的上面，
on the top space,
在最高的间上，
then that's the upper G,
那么它是高音 G ，
so you gotta make sure always be looking at the music,
所以你必须确保一直在看乐谱，
now we're getting into these doubles of notes,
现在我们有了这些双音符，
by the end you'll have two and three of all these notes,
到最后你会有两到三个音符，
they're called octaves,
它们被称为八度，
so you'll have many different octaves by the time we're done.
所以当我们完成时，你会有很多不同的八度。
Okay, now, here's your assignment for this coming, for this session,
好的，现在这是你们这节课的作业，
the things that you need to cover,
你们需要学会的内容，
I want you to do all of the first through the fourth string exercises in your book,
我希望你完成书中第一到第四弦的练习，
play through our songs, that I have listed out there,
弹奏我们的歌曲，我已经列出来了，
Yankee Doodle,
Yankee Doodle ，
When the Saints Go Marching In,
When the Saints Go Marching In ，
and Love me Tender.
和 Love me Tender 。
Now, we'll work on those in the workshop time,
现在，我们将在 workshop 时间讨论这些问题，
so I'll see you there.
在那里见。
Okay, welcome to the workshop time,
好的，欢迎来到 workshop 时间，
this is where I think the work gets done,
我认为这是完成工作的地方，
a lot of guys dream about being a guitar player,
很多人梦想成为一名吉他手，
but here when you're actually doing the practicing
但在这里，当你实际练习的时候，
is what separates dreamers from guys that actually become guitar players,
是梦想者和真正成为吉他手的人的区别，
so let's start going through these exercises,
所以让我们开始练习，
remember what we talked about last time,
记住我们上次说过的，
we have ties, we have dots,
我们有延音线，我们有附点，
ties tie over the bar line
延音线越过小节线，
and you add those two notes together,
你把这两个音符加在一起，
dots what do dots do,
附点做什么，
dots add half of whatever they're attached to,
附点加一半它们连接的东西，
mainly you're going to see it attached to half notes,
主要你会看到它附在二分音符上，
so it would be a dot attached to a half note,
所以在二分音符上加一个附点，
would actually get three beats.
就会得到三个节拍。
Okay, let's start going through some of these exercises,
好的，让我们开始做一些练习，
I'm gonna work with a metronome,
我会用一个节拍器，
like we talked about in our guitar tips section,
就像我们在吉他技巧部分谈到的那样，
just so you can see how working with a metronome really pays off,
你可以看到用节拍器工作是如何获得回报的，
my metronome is set to about 66 beats per minute right now
我的节拍器现在被设置为每分钟 66 个节拍，
and let's go through third string exercises.
我们来做第三弦的练习。
We're going to go through the first one,
我们要做第一个，
remember our notes on the third string, G A,
记得我们在第三弦上的音符， G A ，
let's play together,
让我们一起弹奏，
number one, third string exercises,
第一个第三弦练习，
ready, go.
准备，开始。
To number two,
第二个，
ready play.
准备，弹奏。
Very good, okay, now let's do number three,
非常好，好的，现在让我们做第三个，
ready, play, rest, rest.
准备，弹奏，休息，休息。
Number four, three four time,
第四个， 3 4 拍，
I've switched time signatures on you,
我换了拍号，
it's not always going to be in four four time,
不会总是在 4/4 拍，
some songs are gonna be in three,
有些歌曲会是 3 ，
this has three beats per measure,
这个每个小节有 3 个节拍，
let's do this one,
让我们来做这个，
ready play.
准备，弹奏。
Very good, let's crank it up a little bit,
很好，让我们把它调高一点，
try that last one one more time.
再试一次最后一个。
Now, I'm at about 92
现在我大约 92 拍，
and maybe too fast, let's go back to 80,
也许太快了，让我们回到 80 ，
number four, ready go.
第四个，准备，开始。
Now let's talk about fourth string exercises,
现在，让我们来谈谈第四弦的练习，
remember our notes on the fourth string,
记住我们在第四弦上的音符，
we have D, second finger E, the third finger F.
我们有 D ，食指 E ，无名指 F 。
Okay, let's go through all of our notes,
好的，让我们看一下所有的音符，
just while I'm thinking about, D E F,
我在想， D E F ，
next note, next line G A,
下一个音符，下一个弦， G A ，
next string, B C D,
下一弦， B C D ，
E F G,
E F G ，
let's go backwards.
让我们倒回去。
Fourth string exercise number one,
第四弦练习第一个，
go, one two, two three four.
开始， 1 2 ， 2 3 4 ，
Here you go, number two,
干得好，第二个，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
do remember to alternating your picking.
记得交替你的拨片。
We'll do number three,
我们弹第三个，
ready go.
准备，开始。
And last one, number four,
最后一个，第四个，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
quarter note,
四分音符，
let's do it again.
我们再弹一次。
Let me crank up the tempo a little bit,
让我把节拍器调高一点，
and let's do that number four one more time,
让我们再做一次第四个，
a little bit faster,
快一点，
this is back at 88,
这又回到了 88 ，
one two, ready play,
1 2 ，准备，开始，
do it again.
再来一次，
Very good, let's move on to our songs,
很好，让我们到我们的歌曲，
can I just go through some of the songs that we need to cover for next time,
让我来回顾一下下一次我们需要介绍的一些歌曲，
first one is going to be Yankee Doodle,
第一首是 Yankee Doodle ，
okay, Yankee Doodle that was the first song I learned,
Yankee Doodle 这是我学的第一首歌，
when I was learning guitar, there's Yankee Doodle,
当我学吉他时，就是 Yankee Doodle ，
here we go, let me flip on the metronome here,
我们继续，让我在这里按下节拍器，
I'll go to pretty nice slow events pace for this one,
这次我会使用很慢的速度，
ready, starts on that C,
准备，从 C 开始，
ready play,
准备，弹奏，
next line,
下一行，
here you go, we're going to do one more time,
干得好，我们再弹一次，
give another shot at it,
再试一次，
ready play.
准备，弹奏。
Pretty good, move on the next song,
很好，到下一首歌曲，
When the Saints Go Marching In,
When the Saints Go Marching In ，
okay, now this one starts with the rest,
好的，这首歌从休止符开始，
you want to make sure that you don't play on that first rest,
你要确保你不会弹奏第一个休止符，
a little bit confusing,
有点困惑，
I'll count it off for you,
我会为你倒数，
let's play together.
我们一起弹。
One two three four, rest,
1 2 3 4 ，休息，
two three four, rest,
2 3 4 ，休息，
one two one two,
1 2 1 2 ，
here comes a tie,
这里有一个延音线，
hang onto it, keep that pressure down,
按住它，保持住压力，
one two, here's a dot, two three,
1 2 ，这里有一个附点， 2 3 ，
two three four, one rest,
2 3 4 ， 1 休息，
two three four, one two three four.
2 3 4 ， 1 2 3 4 。
Very good, very good,
非常好，
let me turn this on,
让我打开这个，
let's play one more time,
我们再弹一次，
speed it up a little bit,
再快一点，
one two,
1 2 ，
When the Saints Go Marching In,
When the Saints Go Marching In ，
two, ready and rest,
2 ，准备，休息，
two three four, rest,
2 3 4 ，休息，
two three four, one two,
2 3 4 ， 1 2 ，
two three four, one two three four.
2 3 4 ， 1 2 3 4 。
Last one we need to do is Love me Tender
最后我们要弹的是 Love me Tender ，
or Aura Lee as the older name, it was called,
或者 Aura Lee 是它的原名，
about right there.
就在那里。
One, two, ready, go,,
1 2 准备，开始，
next line, ready, go,,
下一行，准备，开始，
two three four, two three four.
2 3 4 ， 2 3 4 。
Good, speed it up a little bit
好的，把速度加快一点，
and try it one more time.
再试一次。
Ready, one two, ready, play,
准备， 1 2 ，准备，弹奏，
next line, go, this is easy [],
下一行，开始，这是简单的[]，
two three four, two three four.
2 3 4 ， 2 3 4 。
All the practice, you can get is really going to start paying off,
所有的练习你都能得到回报，
as we're coming towards the end of learning these notes on the third and the fourth string.
当我们学习第三弦和第四弦的音符接近尾声时。
So get ready and we will see you next time.
所以做好准备，我们下次再见。